the Super Bowl was this weekend and I
still haven't watched it because I DVR
it two teams from the East Coast flew to
the most boring city in the world to
play the big game Eli's horse-faced
brother was there probably in the same
stable as Tom Brady's horse-faced
wife security really dropped the ball
when some hideous old woman managed to
sneak onto the field during halftime and
started
bogging and don't say you watch the
Super Bowl for the commercials the
world's best athletes are trying to kill
each other and you just shush me to hear
what the planters peut was going to
say congrats to the 9 and S Giants on
the big win a team that couldn't beat
the Redskins in the regular season was
clearly the best team in the world Eli
was truly an inspiration he proved if
you work really hard and your older more
talented brother breaks his neck you can
succeed no matter how mentally
handicapped you
look football is officially over so
let's take a look back at the NFL season
Through The Eyes of its most passionate
and embarrassing fans
[Applause]
you been
unable why are you crying cu the B one
the B
one this is our here I this isn't I was
supposed to happen I hate
this
come on
it
no get out get the out get the out of my
house right now I don't want from any of
you oh my God I don't have to Oakland no
don't look at me they won't make the
playoffs it's hard being a jet F
[Applause]
huh there's always next
year